

Manav Deep Singh Lamba

Experienced in UI/UX and frontend development with a demonstrated history of real life projects. I also hold management positions at several renowned organisations. Currently interning at Unisight technologies and working as freelancer.

I have 2 years experience in Frontend development and UI designing.

Fluent at creating web applications using agile methodologies.

Proficient in software development and producing responsive web designs.









Work Experience



Vice Community Manager • CodeAsylums Network

February 2021 - Present

I'll be overlooking the functioning of entire community and make sure that there is no room for disturbances.

Senior Core



CORE COMMITTEE . CodeChef-VIT, Vellore

December 2019 - Present

I am responsible for designing and developing the websites for the organisation. Also, I design UI for the apps. Moreover my responsibilities extend to look for sponsors and increasing the market reach.



Director of Events • F.E.P.S.I.

December 2019 - Present

I work as a member of design team in one of the initiatives of F.E.P.S.I The name of the initiative is Ullas.



Frontend Developer • Unisight Technologies & CO

March 2021 - March 2021

I will be working as a frontend developer and will be reporting virtually to the project leads and the clients.



Campus Ambassador · Decodr Technologies

July 2020 - January 2021

CORE COMMITTEE



CORE COMMITTEE • Indian Society For Technical Education, VIT Vellore

December 2019 - January 2021

I was answerable to the board for handling marketing and sponsorship. I was also a part of the frontend team.

Education



2019 - 2023

Vellore Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Technology-BTech Information Technology

Skills

- html + css + javascript
- figma UI
- After Effects
- prototype design
- Responsive Web Design

Languages

- English Professional
- Hindi Native or Bilingual